russiandating.ru 2013-11-26

# Privacy Policy

Depending on what you do when you visit any Web site, you are providing information about your visit to the site's owners. This includes RussianDating.ru. We value privacy and think you do too, so we want you to have the information you need to make your own decisions about your personal privacy. When you visit or supply information to any Web site, we think it's a good idea for you to first understand what that site's privacy policies are. If the site doesn't tell you, don't hesitate to ask.

The bottom line at www.RussianDating.ru is that we use the information that we get from your visit for internal tracking purposes, to make RussianDating.ru as useful and interesting to you as we can, and to respond to your requests for information or other services. Except for as specifically noted, we do not use your personal information for any other purpose; we never sell it to any third party; and we never share it with any third party.

## Read more about:

### I. Notice

What personal information we collect and how we use your information Our policy regarding information sharing.

### II. Choice

How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us.

### III. Access

How you can control the use of your personal information.

### IV. Security

How we protect the security of your personal information.

### V. Customer Service and Recourse Changes to the RussianDating.ru Privacy Policy

How to contact RussianDating.ru Protecting Your Privacy Online

### I. Notice

What personal information we collect and how we use your information:  
When you visit the RussianDating.ru Web site, we capture the Internet provider's domain name and country that you came from (e.g., 'aol.com') and the paths taken as you move from page to page (i.e., your "click stream" activity).

Information we collect on RussianDating.ru may be used to enhance your use of this Web site in ways like these:

  1. 1\. Arrange the Web site in the most user-friendly way;
  2. 2\. Customize your browsing experience of this Web site;
  3. 3\. Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices;
  4. 4\. Respond to your question or suggestions Visitor Registration or Requests for Information:

RussianDating.ru only collects personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using or registering with the RussianDating.ru site. "Personal information" includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name or email address; and, in the case of affiliate agreements, your name and company name. While you can browse our site without registering, you will need to register in order to take advantage of certain features.

**Browsing and the use of Cookies:**

RussianDating.ru uses cookie technology as part of our Web site's statistical reporting. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a Web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to personalize your experience (i.e., rotating images on RussianDating.ru home page) and to gather Web site statistical data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded, the internet provider's domain name and country that our visitors come from (e.g. 'aol.com,' or 'umich.edu') and the addresses of sites visited immediately before, and after, coming to RussianDating.ru. However, none of this is associated with you as an individual. It is measured only in aggregate. The information in the cookies lets us trace your "click stream" activity (i.e., the paths taken by visitors to our site as they move from page to page. Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you.

We also use standard Web server log files to help us count visitors and evaluate our site's technical capacity. We use this information to find out how many people visit RussianDating.ru, help us arrange the pages in the most user-friendly way, keep the site browser-friendly, and to make our pages more useful to our visitors. We record information on site traffic but not information on individual visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular will be kept or used.

To browse without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)

**Email, Mailing Lists, and Other Services:**

When you send us an email, we use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use.

When you request information or other services, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or other services you requested until you ask us to stop (using the 'unsubscribe' instructions provided with each email and/or on the site where you signed up and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or service is no longer available. We will not use your address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited message or information (unless that is part of the service you are requesting), nor will we share it with or sell, rent or lease it to any third party for such use.

**Linking To Other Sites:**

Please remember that when you use a link to go from RussianDating.ru to another Web site, the RussianDating.ru Site Rules and this Privacy Policy are no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including any site that has a link on RussianDating.ru, is subject to the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

### Our policy regarding sharing of information:

**Our policy is simple:**

I. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances.

II. Choice How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us: 

If you choose to receive them, RussianDating.ru may periodically send you email messages describing updates, new features, or promotional offers related to this Web site. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time. Simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request. If you do not explicitly choose to receive informational emails, the only email messages you will receive from RussianDating.ru will be to respond to email inquiries that you send us.

III. Access How to update or correct your personal information:

To modify or delete your personal information, simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request, and we will make the requested changes.

IV. Security How we protect the security of your personal information:

The security of your personal information is very important to us and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. RussianDating.ru uses firewalls and has security measures in place at its physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Web site.

V. Customer Service and Recourse Changes to the RussianDating.ru Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy was posted in June 2001. RussianDating.ru reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. We take privacy matters very seriously, and intend to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. We will occasionally update our privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy policy updates.

**How to contact RussianDating.ru:**

Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any RussianDating.ru related services, you consent to RussianDating.ru's processing of this information in the United States/Russia as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating. If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about RussianDating.ru’s privacy policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to contact us.
